Guide to the International Convention records 1908-2006 IBT0019
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Convention Publications, 1906-2006; Series 2; 4.5 Linear Feet
  - Certificate of Affiliation from the Team Drivers' International Union to Teamsters and Drivers of Belleville, Series 2
  - Seventeenth Convention: Report of John F. English, General Secretary-Treasurer, 1957; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Flyers for the 29th international Convention, August 1980 - October 1982; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - DVDs: "Teamsters Unity 2008", "International Brotherhood of Teamsters 28th International Convention, Las Vegas", 2008-2011; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - 28th Convention: Convention News Las Vegas, Nevada, June 27-30, 2011; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - 28th Convention: Event Flyers, 2011; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Hoffa and Hall, IBT Convention News: "Your Convention Scorecards", "Jim Hoffa and Ken Hall Welcome IBT Convention Delegates", 2011-2016; Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Proceedings of the 5th Annual Convention, August 5-13, 1907; IBT 0019 Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Proceedings of the 15th Convention, August, 11-15, 1947; IBT 0019 Series 2 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Constitution adopted by the 23rd International Convention, 1986; Series 2 (Box Shared Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Tenth Report of Officer's Convention, 4 October 1920; Series 2 (Box Shared Box 35, Folder 5)
  - 30th International Convention: Adopted Constitution, 2021 June; Series 2 (Box Shared Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Proceedings of the 29th Convention, 27 July 2016 - 29 July 2016; Series 2 (Box Shared Box 36, Folder 13)
  - 29th Convention: Proposed Constitution, 27 June 2016; Series 2 (Box Shared Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Report to the 29th Convention by the Diversity Committee, 27 June 2016; Series 2 (Box Shared Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Report to the Convention by the Pension & Benefits Committee, 27 June 2016; Series 2 (Box Shared Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Report to the 29th Convention by the Appeals and Grievances Committee, 27 June 2016; Series 2 (Box Shared Box 36, Folder 17)
- Memorabilia, Series 3
  - Central Conference of Teamsters, ND; Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Tele-Views First and Foremost Teleision Magazines, Vol. 7, No. 11; Article "Teamster Union Convention on TV!", November 1952; Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - The International Teamster, Vol. 54, No II, Articles regarding the Seventeenth Convention, 1957 November; Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Delegate Convention Vest, several pins and buttons attached, Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Engraved Walnut Box. Inscription reads "Las Vegas 2001 Teamsters: Building Better Lives. Together. International Brotherhood of Teamsters 26th International Convention". Inside is an engraved gavel and block., 2001 June 25-29; Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - 18th Convention Badge, 1961; IBT 0019 Series 3 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - 19th Convention Badge, 1966; IBT 0019 Series 3 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - 21st Convention Badge, 1976; IBT 0019 Series 3 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - 22nd Convention Badge, 1981; IBT 0019 Series 3 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - 28th Convention Photographs, 2001; IBT 0019 Series 3 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Photograph Book from the 16th Convention, 1952; IBT 0019 Series 3 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - A Gathering of Teamsters: A Look at the First Five Decades of Convention History, 2021; Series 3 (Box Shared Box 35, Folder 7)
- Teamsters All, Series 4
  - Teamsters All, 1976; Series 4 (Box Shared Box 32, Folder 1)